

KEVIN GELLENONCOURT

SOFTWARE ENGINEER
ANGULAR & .NET
INPG ENSIMAG - PHELMA

Computer sciences and applied mathematical trained engineer, empowered with 10 years work experience in IT industry in France. After recently coming to Shenzhen to join my life partner, I am looking for a technical job in the area.

CONTACT

PROFILE

Adress. 134, Songyu Street, Songgang, Bao'an

District, Shenzhen

Mobile. (+86) 152.1776.8244

Mail. Kevin.Gellenoncourt@Gmail.com

LinkedIn. Kévin Gellenoncourt

PORTFOLIO

Web. App.Angular | Api.Net | App.Blazor

Angular, Ngrx, Material | .Net Blazor .Net Api, EFCore, Sqlite | Firebase, Azure

SKILLS

Software Development

Framework.

- .Net [Blazor | Api | Mvc] (5 yrs)
- Angular, Ngrx, Material (4 yrs)
- Java, Spring (3 yrs)

<u>Language.</u> C#, Js, Ts, Html, Css, Sql <u>Database.</u> OracleDb, SqlServer, SqLite <u>Ide.</u> VsCode, Visual Studio, Eclipse <u>Tools.</u> GitLab, TeamCity, AzureDevOps, Jenkins

Business Knowledge

Health | Health Insurance | Real Estate Public Aid | Insurance (Home, Auto...)

Team Management & Documentation

Agile, Jira, Confluence, Teams, Sharepoint

Language

- French. Native
- English. Fluent (Toefl 2011)

Hobby

Learning Chinese | Running | Swimming

EXPERIENCES

Family Proximity

May, 2021 – August, 2023 (~2 years) (France · Grand Est)

- <u>2022-2023.</u> (1 yr. 2 mo.) **Baloise** · **Software Engineer** (*Luxembourg*)
 - User Management Solution Implementation | IdentityServer
 - o Technical Framework Definition App Blazor & Api .Net
 - Legacy Development (Angular & .Net Mvc)
 - <u>Technology.</u> Angular, Ngrx | .Net [Blazor, Api] | Entity
 Framework | SqlServer | .Net Mvc, JQuery, Kendo | Clean
 Architecture
- <u>2021.</u> (8 mo.) **Docaposte** · **Project Technical Manager** (*France, Metz*)
 - Extranet & Web Services Maintenance & Improvement
 - Technical specification, development & testing
 - o Management & Coordination with dev team in Tunisia
 - o Technology. Asp.Net Webform, .Net Framework, PISql, OracleDb

Discover .Net & Front-End Development

September, 2017 – December, 2020 (~3 years) (France, Grenoble)

- 2020. (~1.8 yrs.) Seiitra · Software Engineer
 - o Development of 2 modules « Manage Fees » & « Accounting »
 - o Technical framework definition, design, development & testing
 - o **Technology.** Angular, Bulma, .NetCore 2.2, Bitbucket
- 2019. (~6 mo.) Schneider Electric · Data Architect
 - o Sparql Queries, Data Modeling & Java Development
- 2018. (1 yr.) Hospice Civil de Lyon · Software Engineer
 - o Electronic patient files, doc modules evolution
 - o **Technology.** AngularJS, JQuery, .NetCore 2.x, SqlServer

Discover IT Responsibilities

February, 2013 – April, 2017 (~4 years) (France, Grenoble)

- 2016-2017. (1,5 yrs) Cnam · Project Manager
 - $\circ \quad \text{Managing Activity, Planning, Staff, Finance} \\$
 - o 2017. Technical Support Team (6 pers., 3 products)
 - o 2016. Healthcare professionals Webservices (10 pers., 3 projects)
- 2013-2016. (3 yrs) Cnam · Back-End Software Engineer
 - o Billing Webservices for healthcare professionals
 - o Technical & Business Specification, Development & Testing
 - <u>Technology.</u> Java, Spring (Mvc & Batch), WebLogic, OracleDb

EDUCATION

2013 | Engineering Degree · INP Phelma - Ensimag · France, Grenoble Specialization. Computer Sciences & Telecommunication

2008-2010 | Classe Préparatoires aux Grandes Ecoles · France, Metz Specialization. PTSI/PT (Physique Technique et Science de L'Ingénieur)